[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 11, "question": "Do you actually like pizza?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 12, "answer": "Yes, I love pizza.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Did you say impressive second?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Impressive second.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Is there ever an impressive second?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, yes, because I'm --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "You're a winner, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Yes, I'm a winner.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I mean in business, there's never an impressive second.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Why don't we -- why don't we do it again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Yes, but you won't be happy if you almost become the Republican candidate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Will you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gingrich", "Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Who would you respect the most?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Well, I would say that Speaker Gingrich and Governor Mitt Romney are the two that I have the greatest amount of respect for.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "And who do you have the least respect for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Let's just stick with the one that I have the most respect for.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Because most of his ideas and positions are eliminate, end rather than fix.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "VBN", ",", "CC", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Because most of my career in addition to running organizations, turning around businesses, I have studied, written, and spoken a lot on the topic of leadership.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "NNS", ",", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "And what are your conclusions about Rick Perry and Michele Bachmann?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "When I listen to their answers to questions, most of the time they get off track because they don't -- either don't answer the question or they are not working on the right problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Perry", "Michele Bachmann"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "And you've made a mistake?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "I misspoke.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Did you misspeak or did you make a mistake?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I misspoke.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Did you know what you just said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Benjamin Netanyahu"]}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "But could you be the American president and just sit back over time on these hot issues and say, I don't know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Piers, for me to say whether Benjamin Netanyahu was right or wrong based only on the optics of it is not good judgment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Would you be happy if you were president in Afghanistan, for American military leaders there to continue negotiating and paying Taliban leaders if they felt that it was for the greater good of not necessarily winning the war in Afghanistan, but winning the battle against terrorism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "EX", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "If the commanders on the ground told me that that was a tactic, that they saw was beneficial, I would approve of it because --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan", "Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Taliban"]}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "All the Taliban are terrorists?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Yes, the Taliban are terrorists.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "If you negotiate with them in any capacity, aren't you negotiating with terrorists?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Yes, but you see, some of the people that they are doing some of these things, they are citizens that they are converting to basically be on our side.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Is it more of a mind field morally, ethically, than perhaps you've thought before as you get closer and you start to have to wrestle with all these dilemmas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "CC", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "How do you deal with the element in the Tea Party that is overly racist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Let me say that my experience has been, there is no more a racist element in the Tea Party than there is in the general population at large.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "What do you say to Morgan Freeman, to Harry Belafonte, to others who've been quite vocal about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "I say, go to a Tea Party.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Morgan Freeman", "Harry Belafonte"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NN", "CD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "How po' was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "''", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Well, when your dad was working very, very hard, and we could only get lunch money one day a week to go to grade school, and the other four days our lunch consisted of whatever my mother could scrape together from the dinner the night before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "WP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "What do you remember about that, the fact that you had so little?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "What I remember most about having so little is we appreciated what little we had.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Do you feel that by comparison, most of the people calling themselves poor, have no idea of the kind of poverty that so many -- millions of Americans had to endure that you did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", ":", "NNS", "IN", "NNPS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "I would say that that is true but I don't want to over generalize.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Has it been spoiled?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Some of the population has been spoiled.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ron Paul"]}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "I mean I agree with Ron Paul.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "What about these guys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Those are not the people that were protesting on Wall Street.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "I know some of these people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "They would say it's outrageous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Well, Piers, I did reel against it because the problem is multilevel.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "PERCENT": ["50 percent", "25 percent", "25 percent"]}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "CC", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "How much is the fault of the people themselves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I would say that 50 percent of it is Obama's fault, 25 percent of it is Wall Street's fault, and 25 percent of it is the individual's fault.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Do you think it's a sin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "I think it's a sin because of my biblical beliefs and although people don't agree with me, I happen to think that it is a choice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "You believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I believe that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "You believe people -- seriously, you think people get to a certain age and go, I think I want to be homosexual?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Let me turn it around to you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Where is the -- where is evidence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Just common -- you're a commonsense guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Are you a common sense kind of guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "You genuinely think --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "You haven't given me any evidence to convince me otherwise nor has anyone else.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "You concede I might be right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "That's my -- you might be right, but what I'm saying is this is just my opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "What's your view of abortion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "I believe that life begins at conception.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "No circumstances?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "No circumstances.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "You're mixing --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "NNS", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "I think you would concede, you've backtracked, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Well, you media people call it flip flopping.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "What would you call it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "I call it explaining the intent of my comment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Are there extremist Christians?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "What was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "The media came up with a loyalty test.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "What was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "My test was simply, you have peaceful Muslims, you have extremists.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "From any religion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "From any religion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "What would you say now that you're nearing the stage of possibly being president, to make them feel less concerned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "If you are truly a peaceful Muslim in this country, I have no problem with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Have you learned to be slightly more cautious about how many flags of caution you raise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Not yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "You had no idea you had them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I had no idea that I had tumors in my liver, because when I went to get the cat scan and I got the results, they won't tell you the results.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "When you hear tumors and liver, you're thinking, this could be the end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["30 percent", "70 percent"]}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "When did you realize you were going to make it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "I realized I was going to make it -- first of all, I to go through chemotherapy, double surgery, recuperate from the double surgery, where they took out 30 percent of my colon, 70 percent of my liver, recuperate, go through some more intensive chemotherapy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Why is it your lucky gold tie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Because I believe in the gold standard that we never should have gotten off of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Why don't you like using African-American, by the way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Because as I trace my roots back in this country, the majority of my roots -- the ones that are more meaningful to me were the slaves that were my foreparents, my forefathers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Why was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Because of my age.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sears"]}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "What did you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "I drove over to Sears, bought me some clippers and a set of clippers, and went home and cut the my own hair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Have you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Yes, I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this this morning"]}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Doesn't look too bad, actually?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "I just did this this morning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Will you continue to cut your own hair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "I might not, just because of the time required.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "What are the values that they instilled you in that you would take to the White House?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "First, my faith, belief in God.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RBR", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Into a nice house?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "But more importantly, it provided enough such that after my dad passed at the age of 56, we could take care of my mother comfortably, because she had Alzheimer's.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "POS", "RB", "IN", "NN", "VBG", ",", "PRP$", ",", "PRP$", ",", "PRP$", ",", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "What would they have made of you right now, where you found yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "My mother's probably in heaven going, my, my, my, my.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NN", "CD", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Are you the guy, you think, that could beat him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "I believe that I could beat him, because I think that, number one, my leadership ability would come through even in a debate in terms of how I would approach problems.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Do you actually like pizza?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "Yes, I love pizza.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "Do you eat it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "I do eat it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "What is your favorite pizza?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "AIN: My favorite pizza is to obviously with a nice tangy tomato sauce.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "A bit like you, fiery?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Emotional?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "Passionate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "Meaty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]